export const data = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance? ",
    option1: [1, "Virtual Dom"],
    option2: [2, "Real Dom"],
    option3: [3, "Both 1 and 2"],
    option4: [4, "None of the above"],
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    option1: [2, "User interface Framework"],
    option2: [2, "Server side Framework"],
    option3: [3, "Client side Framework"],
    option4: [4, "Both 1 and 3"],
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
    option1: [1, "Render with arguments"],
    option2: [2, "setState"],
    option3: [3, "props"],
    option4: [4, "propTypes"],
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who created React.js?",
    option1: [1, "Jordan Walke"],
    option2: [2, "Sundar Pichai"],
    option3: [3, "Bill Gates"],
    option4: [4, "Elon Musk"],
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which language is React.js written?",
    option1: [1, "Python"],
    option2: [2, "Javascript"],
    option3: [3, "Php"],
    option4: [4, "Java"],
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Babel?",
    option1: [1, "Javascript Compiler"],
    option2: [2, "Javascript interpreter"],
    option3: [3, "Javascript transpiler"],
    option4: [4, "Javascript files bundler"],
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which language is React.js written?",
    option1: [1, "Python"],
    option2: [2, "Javascript"],
    option3: [3, "Php"],
    option4: [4, "Java"],
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
    option1: [1, "3000"],
    option2: [2, "3036"],
    option3: [3, "8000"],
    option4: [4, "8100"],
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
    option1: [1, "External storage of the component"],
    option2: [2, "The internal storage of the component"],
    option3: [3, "Permanent storage"],
    option4: [4, "None of the above"],
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      " Among The following options, choose the one which helps react for keeping their data uni-directional?",
    option1: [1, "DOM"],
    option2: [2, "Flux"],
    option3: [3, "JSX"],
    option4: [4, "Redux"],
    ans: 2,
  },
];
